foreign
国外
we'll be using masking with Kaden live
我们将与卡登一起使用面具直播
to have some text revealed from behind
让一些文字从后面显示出来
an object in our video
我们视频中的一个物体
we can do this a couple different ways
我们可以用几种不同的方法来做这件事
so here's another example of a car
这是另一个汽车的例子
revealing the text but for this one
如果不是因为这一次 就会揭示文本
we're going to be doing this tree video
我们要制作这段树视频
clip we'll drag it down to the timeline
我们会把它拖到时间线上
and this is just a camera moving panning
这只是一个摄像机移动平移
past a tree and we want our text to be
经过一棵树 我们希望我们的文本是
behind the tree and then show up as we
在树的后面 然后出现在我们
kind of come around it so we'll go to to
绕过它 所以我们要去
create a title clip
创建字幕剪辑
and we could really reveal any object
我们真的可以揭示任何物体
but in this case it's text so we'll
但在这种情况下 它是文本 所以我们将
create a title clip which type the word
创建一个输入单词的标题剪辑
forest and then we'll make sure that
森林 然后我们会确保
this title clip is the same length as
此标题剪辑的长度与
our video clip or at least
我们的视频片段 或者至少
the portion that we want to be revealed
我们想要展示的那部分
at
在…
and we can transform this text to make
我们可以把这篇文章转化成
it a little bit larger if we want to
如果我们想的话它会更大一点
and then go open the search bar here and
然后打开这里的搜索栏
type in mask under effects and we'll
在效果下键入遮罩 我们将
drag this rotoscoping mask over top of
将这个对位口罩拖到顶部
the text clip
文本剪辑
and so what this lets us do is draw a
因此 这让我们可以绘制一个
mask on top of this text clip and it
此文本剪辑顶部的蒙版和它
also create a key frame so the first
还可以创建一个关键帧 以便第一个
point that we draw we'll get to the
我们画的这一点 我们将到达
point right where the text is about to
指向正文即将出现的位置
come out of the tree and we'll just draw
从树上出来 我们只需抽签
sort of a box around the text
文本周围有一个方框
and then we'll change the alpha
然后我们会改变阿尔法
operation to subtract and then we can go
做减法运算 然后我们就可以走了
to the point where we think the text is
到了我们认为文本是
going to be completely revealed
将会完全揭晓
and notice we don't see anything until
注意 我们什么都看不到 直到
we adjust the mask and then by adjusting
我们调整蒙版 然后通过调整
this anything outside of it will be
它之外的任何东西都将是
visible since we did the subtract and
因为我们做了减法和
anything inside of it will be not
里面的任何东西都不会是
visible
可见
and then we can just come over here on
然后我们就可以来这里了
the timeline and it created a keyframe
时间线 它创建了一个关键帧
for us automatically but it wasn't
对我们来说是自动的 但它不是
exactly perfect and so we can kind of go
非常完美 所以我们可以说
along and adjust this mask through over
沿着并调整这个蒙版 直到
the timeline and every time I make an
时间线 每次我做一次
adjustment it'll create a keyframe
调整它将创建一个关键帧
between the last point that we made an
在我们提出的最后一点之间
adjustment and the next point we're
调整和下一步我们将
making an adjustment and it'll sort of
做一个调整 它就会有点
estimate where it thinks that it's not
估计在它认为不是的地方
really looking at where the tree is it's
真的在看树在哪里它在哪里
just looking at the difference between
只需看看两者之间的区别
where we moved it's just using keyframes
我们移动的位置只是使用了关键帧
to adjust that mask in between those
要调整介于这两个之间的遮罩
points so notice down in the timeline
在时间线上注意到的几点
different keyframes are being created
正在创建不同的关键帧
these red ones are the active ones and
这些红色的是活跃的和
also on the effects panel you can see
在效果面板上 您还可以看到
the keyframes too
关键帧也是如此
and with this clip it's fairly easy
有了这段视频 就很容易了
because it's moving at a constant speed
因为它在以恒定的速度移动
so the masking isn't incredibly
所以面具并不是令人难以置信的
difficult
困难
if you want to follow along with this
如果你想跟上这一步
exact video clip you can find a download
准确的视频剪辑 你可以找到一个下载
link for it in the video description
视频描述中的链接
once you get to the point where you feel
一旦你到了你感觉到
like the masking is done pretty well you
就像面具做得很好一样
can go ahead and play your video
可以继续播放您的视频
I hope this video has made it a little
我希望这段视频能让我有一点
more clear about how to use the masking
更清楚地了解如何使用掩码
to reveal objects in Caden live if you
如果要在Caden LIVE中显示对象 请执行以下操作
have any questions or comments please
如有任何问题或意见 请
leave them below and look forward to
请将它们留在下面 并期待
catching you in the next video
在下一个视频中看到你